Good day, let me tell you where you are tracking the momentum.
You are here today, so
see, Mama entry numbers are very
good, so short term money has moved into that, but it is still thinking of
Bank Sargam
Russia. I am telling you that Bank Nifty is going to reach 37,000,
whether it comes in 15 days or a
month, but there are students in the bank and a lot
in the media department. The
commentary that has come today from Bandhan Bank and Mitra Mandal
Microfinance is saying that landing is bad,
recovery is 25 percent. Anoop
Chamber tweets 98% management etc. diseases, I am
commenting. Bandanwar Belan, make it
famous in IDFC. You will be rich. I will give
you an update on the reported midcap bank Rubaru Circle. I had given you 1958 finance of
95.5 Vidya, book profit in that
and but you have two pieces of ₹2 handsome.
Here I should also say that for Tube Bank of 1035,
I gave a target of 1150, it has become 1185,
which is probably Micro Finance Law and
Urban Bank and Guntur Extremely Well  Today there are
two pieces, if you say so, start now phone
ji machine safe badh
hello friends, the first one will be ICICI
Lombard Insurance from the ground and
Insurance Guddu Yadav stream
ICICI Lombard after getting 1658
character 215 34540 for which
stoploss is 1510 12 this is going back to 1000
behind my favorite updates UP Bank of
Baroda Bank of Baroda will
give the highest record profit in this quarter which is your July
end because of health in eighty-four,
take that bus stop love 7250 decided to
₹90 then
ambulance packing machine sa aa from Bank of Baroda on long reference today's
hot topic of discussion is in innovation, should we
invest money in the IPO of matches which has been run, see this in its price point of 7276,
Harshita
was telling all the trends, stands and friends let's
everyone this parking rate price to
perfection body stock will  Make money over the
next few years to figure out where it's headed
and used to give you a little bit of context. If you're not writing
this off, it's a no-brainer. Like I told you, there's no
metric for its valuation before, so it's
difficult to comment,
but I think you should invest in your portfolio
in small quantities. I'm taking this very
conservative view. For now, I think
midcap IT is a good
reason. You're seeing such tremendous momentum in midcap IT. So, I'm taking
this ruling.
Score for a reminder. We've gone from a very low level.
Still, I think what's the real deal? Should I go
into National Tech Mahindra today? Will it give you something? But
today, I'm buying
students. Lapet Yadav. Banking stocks,
if I see Bank of Baroda at 140, I'll
focus on that. Or RBL, I see it at
400. I see it at 350.
And so, I'm very interested in midcap banks. And
this is the only one, but I like it. I've
admitted that the party has been very, very
big.  Outperformer and observation
drinks ringgit the real ball will commit
midcap bank listen to mixture banks bandhan
bank of baroda and machine sir on bell for a long
time you are also seeing a pistol and technical call
next 50 minutes have passed